// This is the file that contains all the question, answer and point value data.

var json = [{
	// Game 1 Question 1
	"question": "Who is Will Rodgers?",
	"answers": ["Creative Services Director", "Actor/Singer", "I don't know", "Cowboy", "The Man", "His father's son"],
	"points": [48, 22, 20, 16, 4, 2]
},{
	// Game 1 Question 2
	"question": "In 3 words or less, how does the internet work?",
	"answers": ["Magic", "ISP, Router, Client", "Serices of Tubes", "Everyone's Computers Linked", "Data Flowing Everywhere", "Really Really Fast", "Cat memes", "Through Al Gore"],
	"points": [20, 14, 12, 10, 10, 8, 6, 4]
},{
	// Game 1 Question 3
	"question": "What do the letters CMS stand for?",
	"answers": ["Content Management System", "Customer Management System", "Cloud Management Services", "Client Management Solutions"],
	"points": [76, 18, 4, 4]
},{
	// Game 1 Question 4
	"question": "If Q2 had a mascot, what would it be?",
	"answers": ["Money Clip-$", "The Monopoly Man", "Qbert", "The Letter Q", "Lego Man", "Puppy/Dog", "Dinosour/T-Rex"],
	"points": [10, 8, 6, 6, 6, 6, 4]
},{
	// Game 2 Question 1
	"question": "Other than Will Rodgers, name someone on the Creative Services team.",
	"answers": ["I Don't Know", "Summer Brow", "Rainbough Phillips", "Nicole Field", "Akeem Mason", "Alex Temple", "Diane Calmes"],
	"points": [28, 16, 10, 6, 6, 6, 6]
},{
	// Game 2 Question 2
	"question": "How did you find out that Santa is not real?",
	"answers": ["Wait, What?!", "Siblings", "Found The Loot", "School Friends", "I Guessed", "I Don't Remember", "Grandma/Mom Ate His Cookies", "I'm Jewish"],
	"points": [24, 20, 14, 14, 10, 10, 8, 1]
},{
	// Game 2 Question 3
	"question": "What does Creative Services do?",
	"answers": ["Websites & Styles OLB", "Creates Stuff", "Websites & FI Marketing Collateral", "UUX Colors & Theme", "Q2 Marketing", "Innovative Design", "I Don't Know", "Drink Coffee & Ponder The Universe"],
	"points": [22, 16, 14, 12, 10, 8, 8, 1]
},{
	// Game 2 Question 4
	"question": "You have to replace your hands, other than feet what do you have for hands?",
	"answers": ["Prosthetics", "Lobster Claws", "Tentacles", "Swiss Army Tool", "Eyes/Mouths/Ears", "Tongs", "Harry Potter Wizardy Wand"],
	"points": [24, 10, 8, 6, 6, 6, 2]
},{
	// Game 3 Question 1
	"question": "What is the best feature you have seen on a website?",
	"answers": ["Simplicity/Quick Links/Intuitive", "Live Chat", "Working Buttons", "Saved Passwords/Auto Fill", "Filters"],
	"points": [18, 10, 8, 6, 4]
},{
	// Game 3 Question 2
	"question": "What is Hank's spirit animal?",
	"answers": ["Bear", "Deer/Elk", "Hog", "Lion", "Eagle", "Tiger", "Honey Badger"],
	"points": [24, 18, 8, 8, 8, 4, 4]
},{
	// Game 3 Question 3
	"question": "Who has the coolest name at Q2?",
	"answers": ["Boogie", "Will Ferrell", "Desiree Cries For Ribs", "Matt Flake", "Sunshine Webster", "Adam Blue", "Thi Vo", "Bruce Dragoo"],
	"points": [22, 14, 12, 10, 8, 6, 4, 4]
},{
	// Game 3 Question 4
	"question": "Name one item you have re-gifted",
	"answers": ["Gift Card", "Candle/Candle Holder", "Never Have", "Booze", "Baby Clothes/Toys", "Painting/Picture Frame", "A Shirt"],
	"points": [18, 14, 14, 12, 8, 6, 6]
}
	//...Append additional questions here
];